{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "0 pitanje :",
      "answer": ["da", "ne", "ne", "ne"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },

    {
      "question": "1 pitanje :",
      "answer": ["da", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },

    {
      "question": "2 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["da", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "3 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["da", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },

    {
      "question": "4 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["da", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "5 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["da", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "6 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "7 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "8 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "9 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "10 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "11 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "12 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "13 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["ne", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "14 pitanje:",
      "answer": ["daaa", "ne", "ne", "da"],
      "correctAns": 0
    }
  ]
}
